Rayhan Noufal Arayilakath

Fullstack Web Developer

16016 Lagos St. Justin, TX rayhnouf@gmail.com

SKILLS

In my years of experience, I learned how to effectively and efficiently oversee people, projects, and conflicts. Past knowledge and out-of-the-box thinking allows me to derive the best out of people and give a project the ability to perform at its peak. I also have top-notch skills in development, graphic-design, and UI/UX creation.

EXPERIENCE

Broadcasting and Journalism Club, Westlake Academy - Club Leader

AUGUST 2021 - PRESENT TIME

- Responsible for organizing club members, equipments, deadlines, and funds for the club in its startup period
- In charge of teaching students of varying skill levels how to use various equipment, knowledge on editing tools, and creation of broadcasts.

Open Source Gallery, Fiveable - Open Source Contributor

APRIL 2020 - MAY 2020

- Raised issues with ideas and solutions on the Glthub repository
- Developed a data solution that efficiently pulled information from the Github API and submitted a pull request that was accepted.

Forge Doctors Robotics, Westlake Academy - Team President

AUGUST 2020 - JANUARY 2021

- Responsible for setting deadlines and managing all four aspects of the robotics team, a total of 40+ members across two class periods
- Worked closely with school administration and competition supervisors to get the team set up for competitions in a COVID-19 safe fashion

EDUCATION

Westlake Academy IB World School - Sophomore

AUGUST 2020 - PRESENT

I am currently attending the 10th Grade at Westlake Academy. I have 14 credits worth of classes and my GPA stands at 4.0 (100.277 on 100 point scale).

AWARDS

Some awards that I have received in **High School** related to the position I'm applying for include:

• The **Blacksmith Award** - given to students at Westlake Academy who displayed all IB learner profile traits over the course of the entire school year. The highest award presented to students at the school.

Some awards that I have received in **Middle School** related to the position I'm applying for include:

- The Participation Award for TMSCA State given to students who participated in the state Math and Science Tournament
- the **Presidential Award for Education** given to students who perform exceptionally well at school
- the Outstanding Achievement Award for Digital Graphics and Animation given to a sole student who performed exceptionally well in a subject
- the National Junior Honor Society Certificate of Membership certifies the student is part of the school NJHS chapter

Some awards that I have received in **Elementary School** related to the position I'm applying for include:

- a WOSO (Wayne-Oakland Science Olympiad) Finals medalist for winning in the events
 - Source Code an event where students compete to answer as many questions as possible pertaining to the year's coding language (2017 Language - Java)
 - Simple Machines an event where students compete in pairs to answer as many questions as possible pertaining to the six simple machines
 - Bridging the Gap an event where students compete in a team to engineer a bridge using random craft resources that would have to withstand increasing weights
- the **Certificate of Merit/Award for being a PeaceBuilder** given to students who exhibited leadership traits and kindness during their school year